belchfire.net 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy - Windows XP Themes, Windows Vista Themes, Windows 7 Themes, Desktop Themes

Admin  

Group: Admin

Posts: 9,941

Joined: 17-July 04

From: Calgary, AB, Canada

Member No.: 2

>   
>  **Your privacy is important.**
> 
>   
> 
>   * At Belchfire.net, we know that your privacy is important to you.   
>  It is important to us too. That is why we want you to know about the   
>  personal information we collect, how we use that information and with   
>  whom it may be shared. 
>   
>  

> 
>   
>  **You are always in control.**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * The only personal information that we collect is information that   
>  you give us when you register. We use that   
>  information to service your account and to personalize your experience   
>  at Belchfire.net. We'll never share that information with third parties   
>  interested in e-mailing you or send you our own promotional offer   
>  e-mails without your consent. To see (or change) your information, just   
>  visit the   
>  [My   
>  Controls](http://themes.belchfire.net/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00)  
>  page at Belchfire.net (you will need to do this for   
>  each account, if you have more than one).  
> 
>   
>  

> 
>   
>  **Here is the information we gather:**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * When you register at the site, we ask for certain basic information   
>  to service your account: your e-mail address and a membername and   
>  password. You can change this information using the  
>  [My   
>  Controls](http://themes.belchfire.net/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00) page (under Personal Profile --> Edit Profile Info). You   
>  can change any of this information at any time.
>   
> 
>   * You have the option to use certain services which may require you to provide us with   
>  transmittal information for your friends or family. We only use this   
>  information to provide the requested service.
>   
> 
>   * We also keep track of users' traffic patterns and   
>  related site usage inside our website to help us manage promotions and   
>  advertising, and improve our web page and site design.
>   
> 
>   * From time to time, we may randomly contact members about   
>  participating in a survey about our website. These surveys are optional,   
>  and we use the responses to help us identify users' needs and concerns   
>  so that we can improve or develop new services on the website.
>   
> 
>   * We may also contact members by email in the event of important   
>  system updates or changes.  Members can opt-out of receiving   
>  these messages at any time by de-selecting the 'Send me any updates   
>  sent by the board administrator' option in  
>  [My   
>  Controls](http://themes.belchfire.net/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00) \--> Options --> Email Settings.
>   
> 
>   * While members' email addresses are not publicly viewable anywhere   
>  on Belchfire.net, members can send email to other members using a   
>  web-based form.  Members can choose not to receive email from   
>  other members by selecting the option that reads 'Hide my email   
>  address from other members' in  
>  [My   
>  Controls](http://themes.belchfire.net/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00) \--> Options --> Email Settings.
>   
>  

> 
>   
>  **What you should know about cookies:**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * Cookies are small pieces of information that we send through your   
>  browser to your hard drive. Belchfire.net uses cookies to let us recognize you and provide a more meaningful   
>  and personalized experience when you logon to our site.
>   
> 
>   * Most web browsers are set to accept cookies automatically, but you   
>  can change this setting. See your browser's "help topics" to learn how   
>  to change the setting.
>   
> 
>   * If you decide not to accept cookies, you will still be able to visit our site, but some sections and services on Belchfire.net may not display or work properly for you. Cookies allow   
>  you to take full advantage of the features of Belchfire.net, so we   
>  recommend that you keep them "on."  
> 
>   
>  

> 
>   
>  **With whom is information shared?**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * We may release specific personal information for the following   
>  reasons:
>   
>  
  
> 
>
>>   
> 
>> 
>>   
> 
>>   1. We use outside companies to provide you with some of the services you use on our site as   
>  well as for managing some of our internal operations such as   
>  databases, data analysis and e-mails. As a result, these companies   
>  do have access to the specific information necessary to provide you   
>  with your goods or services, but we require them to keep this   
>  information confidential and not to use it for any other reason.
>>   
> 
>>   2. We will release your personal information to the proper persons when   
>  we believe, in good faith, that we are required to comply with a law   
>  or legal process, enforce our user agreements, or protect the   
>  rights, property or safety of Belchfire.net or other persons or   
>  entities.
>>   
>  
  
> 
> 
>   
>  **Aggregate Statistics.**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * From time to time we provide aggregate statistics about our members,   
>  site traffic and other site-related information to reputable   
>  companies. "Aggregate" is the key word here. You can be assured that we   
>  never include information that allows these companies to identify you   
>  individually.  
> 
>   
>  

> 
>   
>  **E-Mail Addresses.**  
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * We never rent or sell your name and e-mail address to other on-line   
>  marketers of products or services without your consent. You make the   
>  decisions on how you would like to hear from us and if you are   
>  interested in receiving our newsletter and any valuable offers from reputable marketers   
>  of products and services. You can change your preference at any time by   
>  going to your  
>  [  
>  My Controls](http://themes.belchfire.net/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00) page at Belchfire.net (you will need to do this for each account, if you have more than one).
>   
>  

> 
> **Postal Mailing Lists.**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * We do not collect or make your postal address available to anyone for   
>  any reason.
>   
>  

> 
> **External Sites.**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * Belchfire.net may run sweepstakes with select companies or place   
>  advertisements or other promotional offers from select companies on our   
>  website or in our emails. When you choose to participate in these   
>  sweepstakes or promotional offers, you may link to these businesses'   
>  websites and be asked to give them personal information or we may send   
>  over your personal information if you enter it on the Belchfire.net   
>  website. These businesses operate independently from Belchfire.net. Any   
>  personal information that is given to them is at your option and is no   
>  longer controlled by our privacy policy. To avoid confusion, we will   
>  identify these businesses as independent from Belchfire.net, if the   
>  information entry point is inside of the Belchfire.net's website. We   
>  encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies, if you should   
>  have any concerns about how they will care for your personal   
>  information. 
>   
>  

> 
> **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * Belchfire.net is a website directed to the general public. We do   
>  not knowingly collect information from children under 13. 
>   
>  

> 
> **Consent.**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * By using Belchfire.net and providing us with your personal   
>  information, you are accepting the privacy practices described in this   
>  policy statement. 
>   
> 
>   * We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check   
>  back here occasionally. You will always find the latest version posted   
>  here. Updates to our Privacy Policy that would affect how we treat your   
>  personal information will not apply to information collected before we   
>  made the update, unless we first obtain your consent. 
>   
> 
>   * Please note that because a user information database is   
>  customarily considered a business asset, Belchfire.net shall have the   
>  right to transfer it in a merger or sale of some or all of its company   
>  or in an action for bankruptcy. Your information will continue to be   
>  treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy by the acquiring or   
>  merged company unless you are notified and provided an opportunity to   
>  opt of any changes.
>   
>  

> 
> **Disputes.**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * Disputes regarding this policy and the enforcement and adherence   
>  thereof are handled by Belchfire.net. Email  
>  [webmaster@belchfire.net](mailto:webmaster@belchfire.net) if   
>  you believe we are not adhering to this privacy policy and we will   
>  investigate and correct as necessary.
>   
>  

> 
> **Comments.**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy,   
>  please send us an e-mail at [  
>  webmaster@belchfire.net](mailto:webmaster@belchfire.net). 
>   
>  

> 
> **References:**
> 
>   
> 
> 
>   
> 
>   * Our compact privacy policy is sent to one's web browser in the HTTP   
>  headers of each web page requested. Our compact privacy policy is:   
>  **CAO DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa OUR BUS IND UNI COM NAV INT**.
>   
> 
>   * An explanation of our compact privacy policy can be found  
>  [here](http://themes.belchfire.net/w3c/policy.html).
>   
>  

> 
> We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
